Contact

9408870434 (Mobile) monali.rakhasiya@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/monali-rakhasiya-77793473 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Engineering
iOS Development
iPhone Application Development

Languages

Hindi (Full Professional)

English (Professional Working)

Monali Rakhasiya

iOS Apps Developer | Objective C | Swift Gujarat

Summary

Working professional having more than 6.7 years of experience in iOS mobile application development. I got a chance to work on different domain like Insurance, Banking, Mobile Recharge Payments, Car Parking etc. I have been extensively working with objective c and then swift to design highly scalable ios apps, having experience deploying and maintain it on app store. Payment gateway integrations, Google Maps Integrations, AR and VR are some of the areas of interest of mine.

Experience

Brainvire Infotech Inc.
Sr. software engineer
July 2019 - Present (1 year 9 months)
Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

- Working as Sr. iPhone developer
- R&D, Designing user interfaces, coding, implemented third party library, unit testing, deploying application on app store
- Working as single developer for application, as a team member, giving training to junior developers,
- worked on google maps, Moya, MVC, MVVM, MVP, Viper Structure, Firebase push notification, Login with Social medias, Firebase tracking events, Deep linking, Multi targets for single application, implemented UPT
- Familiar with scrum agile methodology
- Working with Jenkins for CICD builds high level.
- YouGo, GETCrew, MAWQIF are applications on which i worked on.

Honing Consultants Sr. IPhone developer April 2017 - July 2019 (2 years 4 months) Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

- Worked as full time senior iPhone application developer.
- Working as Sr. iPhone developer

- R&D, Designing user interfaces, coding, implemented third party library, unit testing, deploying application on app store
- Working as single developer for application, as a team member, giving training to junior developers,
- Familiar with scrum agile methodology
- QualiCost, Labim are applications which i worked upon.

Hightec IT Solution iPhone Developer April 2015 - March 2017 (2 years) Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

- Worked as full time senior iPhone application developer.
- R&D, Designing user interfaces, coding, implemented third party library, unit testing, deploying application on app store
- Working as single developer for application, as a team member, giving training to junior developers.
- worked on KHIDMATI, 4Motors, KEFAN, MAKI, LTS applications.

TechDoodles Jr. iPhone Developer August 2014 - February 2015 (7 months)

Ahmedabad

- worked on designing and building iphone applications.

Education

B H Gardi College of Engineering & Technology
Bachelor of Engineering (BE), Electronics and Communications
Engineering · (2011 - 2014)

Gujarat Technological University Diploma of Education